VALER **MASCA**

2488 Snow Lane, Redding, CA 96003 · 530.691.6750 · valer.masca@gmail.com

GitHub Portfolio: https://github.com/valimasca | LinkedIn Profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/vali-l-masca

Creative and engaging full stack developer with a passion for front-end and back-end development. Specializes in customer satisfaction through teamwork and maintains a commitment to exceed expectations. Self-starter with proven drive, highly focused, and attentive to details. Actively pursuing opportunities to provide programming skills, leadership ability, and enthusiasm to a fast-paced environment as a full stack developer.

SKILLS

Languages / Frameworks / Technologies / Other Skills

HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript (JS) | TypeScript (TS) | jQuery | Bootstrap | ES6 | AngularJS | Angular 6 | React.JS | React Native | Redux | NoSQL | MySQL | SQL server | Node | Express | MongoDB | Mongoose | Passport | Visual Studio Code | Git | GitHub | Slack | Trello | MVC | NPM | Responsive Web Design | Dependency Injection | WebAPI | REST | AJAX | JSON | XML | AWS | Salesforce | Cordova and Ionic | Agile Project Management | Agile Methodologies | Scrum Methodologies | Excel | Microsoft Office | Troubleshooting with Mac OSX and Windows | Leadership | Event Management | Collaboration | Axios

EDUCATION

Bethel School of Technology, Powered by Woz U

- Jan 2019-Sept 2019
- Learned how to build robust web applications using JavaScript, React and Angular
- Acquired skills to program using JavaScript
- Built database-driven web applications using Node.JS and MongoDB
- Created richly interactive client-side apps using the JavaScript React.JS library
- Worked 30-50+ hours weekly on individual and team projects

PROJECTS

ID Card

- My first project during Bethel School of Technology
- A user can input data to create an ID. I used JavaScript, HTML AND CSS
- https://github.com/valimasca/Card-ID

Personal Website

- My first single-page website created during the second module at Bethel School of Technology
- Frameworks used: HTML, CSS, jQuery, AJAX, and JavaScript
- https://github.com/valimasca/My-first-personal-website

AJAX

- My first AJAX project during the second module at Bethel School of Technology
- Learned how to display information on a webpage through an AJAX request
- https://github.com/valimasca/AJAX

Final Project with Bethel School of Technology: Task Ticket

- Final group project for school, working alongside 3 other colleagues from Bethel School of Technology
- The biggest challenge that I overcame was learning how to implement Axios.
- Worked on the back-end with Node.JS, Express.JS, but also contributed to the front-end build with React
- Back-end: https://github.com/bethel-school-of-technology/taskticket-backend
- Front-end: https://github.com/bethel-school-of-technology/taskticket-frontend
- Deployment: http://taskticket.s3-website-us-west-1.amazonaws.com

EXPERIENCE

Data Entry Clerk in Advancement Department, Bethel Church, Redding, California

May 2019-Current

- Entering data inside Salesforce CRM platform
- Managing receipts and reimbursements for field officers

Discharge Coordinator & Healthcare Assistant, National Health Services, England

Jan 2011-Oct 2018

- Worked closely with software and systems provided by Cisco
- Consistently worked in a fast-paced environment
- Served as the lead Discharge Coordinator in surgical ward